midfirst.com 2005-12-14

# Privacy Statement - MidFirst Bank

  | 

MIDFIRST BANK CUSTOMER INFORMATION DISCLOSURE

As required by the Fair Credit Reporting Act and the Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act, this disclosure provides information about the collection, use, sharing and security of nonpublic personal information about you by MidFirst Bank ("we"). This disclosure applies to you if we provide one or more products or services to you to be used primarily for personal, family or household purposes. The information practices described in this disclosure do not apply to (1) products or services used for business purposes or (2) mortgage loans serviced by our affiliate Midland Mortgage Co. 

**Collection of Information About You**

We collect various types of information about you in order to provide products and services requested by you, to process transactions initiated by you in connection with your existing products and services, and to provide you with information about other products and services that we believe may be of interest to you. Examples of the types of information we collect about you are as follows: 

|  |   | Information we receive from you on applications or other forms, such as information about your assets, income and debt;  
---|---|---  
|  | Information about your transactions and experiences with us and with our affiliates, such as account balances and payment history, and correspondence;  
|  | Information we receive from consumer reporting agencies, such as credit history with others and credit worthiness;  
|  | Information from other sources, such as responses from employers, creditors or insurers to inquiries made by us in order to verify your representations to us.  
  
**Use and Sharing of Information About You**

Information about you may be shared within MidFirst Bank in order to provide products and services requested by you, to process transactions initiated by you, or to provide you with information about other products and services offered by us that we believe may be of interest to you;

MidFirst Bank may share information about you with our "affiliates, " which are businesses related to us by common ownership or control. In order to provide you with the products and services you have requested, we may share information about you with our affiliates that perform certain activities on our behalf to service your account. We may also share information about you with our affiliates in order to provide you with information about financial products and services that we believe may be of interest to you. Information about you that we share with our affiliates is limited to transaction and experience information, and other information that is not a "consumer report" as defined in the Fair Credit Reporting Act. If at any time we desire to share information about you with our affiliates other than as described above or as otherwise permitted by law, we will give you notice and the opportunity to restrict the information sharing, as required by the Fair Credit Reporting Act.

Under certain circumstances as specified below, MidFirst Bank may share information about you with "nonaffiliated third parties," which are other companies or individuals not related to us by common ownership or control.

**Other Instances In Which We May Disclose Information About You.**

There are situations in which we are permitted or required by law to disclose your information to third parties. For example, we may disclose information about you to credit bureaus and similar organizations or to government officials as required or permitted by law. We may also disclose information about you in order to record our security interest in the public record. We may disclose information to third parties who assist us in enforcing our rights in connection with your account, who assist us in managing risk, or who are purchasing your account. Finally, we may disclose information about you to third parties with your consent to do so.

We reserve the right to disclose information about you in all of the above and other circumstances as allowed or required by law. Other than as described in this disclosure or as otherwise allowed or required by law, we do not disclose information about you . If at any time we desire to share information about you with nonaffiliated third parties other than as described above or as otherwise permitted by law, we will first give you notice and the opportunity to restrict the information sharing, as required by the Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act.

We will comply with applicable state laws with regard to privacy of information about you.

**Security of Information About You**

We maintain procedures whereby companies that receive nonpublic personal information about you from us are required to maintain it in a secure manner and use it only for the purpose for which it was provided. Our employees are trained regarding the importance of customer financial privacy and proper handling of confidential information. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to reasonably guard your nonpublic personal information. Additionally, we restrict access to nonpublic personal information about you to those employees who have a business reason for accessing that information.

Cookies are pieces of information about your internet usage stored directly on your computer. MidFirst does not use cookies to collect personal data. We use "session cookies" in some instances in order to ensure that you remain on the same server during your browsing session, in order to facilitate your midfirst.com browsing experience. Even though session cookies don't collect personal information, we set them to expire within a day of usage, and no personal data is collected or retained. Websites that are linked to midfirst.com or websites that offer products and services to MidFirst customers may or may not use cookies to collect personal data. If the web address (URL) does not begin with "www.midfirst," then you are on a third party website and you should check the privacy policy or online practices information for that website to learn how cookies are used.

_If you close your account(s) or become an inactive customer, we will adhere to the information practices as described in this notice._
